insuremeonline.com 2010-12-26

# InsureMeOnline.com | Insurance Quotes Free From Top Carriers

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) discloses the privacy practices for [InsureMeOnline.com](http://www.insuremeonline.com/) (the “Site”), and InsureMeOnline.com, LLC (the “Company”) web site and informs you about: 

  * (1) what personally identifiable information is collected;
  * (2) what organization is collecting the information;
  * (3) how the information is used and disclosed to third parties;
  * (4) what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;
  * (5) how to correct, update or delete personally identifiable information; and 
  * (6) what kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the Company’s control.

“Personally identifiable information” is information that would allow someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your full name, address, telephone number or email address. 

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to Customer Assistance by email at [support@insuremeonline.com](mailto:support@insuremeonline.com). 

We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy only addresses our activities in connection with the Site. Other sites (including those that we link to and third party sites that we co-brand) may have their own policies, which we do not control, and thus are not addressed by this Privacy Policy. 

**(1) What Information Is Collected**   
You may provide certain personal information to us when you: (a) request an insurance quote, (b) enroll to receive services; (c) send email messages, submit forms or send other information to us; (d) submit content to the Site; and/or (f) request marketing materials from the Site. We may collect personal information from you at other points on the Site that state that personal information is being collected. We may also receive certain personal information from some of our co-branded third party partners. In the event of a complaint, we may also receive personally identifiable information about you from other parties in our network or from other users or third parties who may communicate information to us about you in relation to that complaint. 

In addition, our servers automatically collect information about which sites users visit and which pages are viewed within the Site, but in these instances, we do not obtain personally identifiable information about you. We use a feature of your browser called a “cookie” to assign a user ID that automatically identifies your computer when you visit the Site. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on the Site. We use cookies for two reasons. First, cookies enable a visitor to have a more unique and enriching experience while visiting the Site. For example, if a visitor requests that the web pages be delivered to the visitor in a specific language a cookie will be used to record this information so that the visitor does not need to specify his or her language preference for each web page that is delivered to the visitor’s browser. Second, we use cookies to track a visitor’s navigation through the Site. This helps us understand how the Site is being used. 

Most browsers will allow a user to refuse cookies. Check your browser’s options for this feature. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, you may not be able to use all of the features of the Site. 

**(2) What Organization Is Collecting the Information**   
The Company owns and operates the Site and is the organization that collects personal information on the Site. Our mailing address is P.O. Box 7276, Woodland Park, Co 80863 and our email address is [support@insuremeonline.com](mailto:support@insuremeonline.com). 

**(3) How the Information Is Used and Disclosed to Third Parties**   
As a general practice, we do not provide your personally identifiable information to third parties. So, for example, we do not sell your email address or your name and personal demographic information to mass marketers. However, on particular pages where we ask for your personally identifiable information, we may explicitly tell you that the data we are collecting on that page will be shared with third parties, in which case those disclosures shall override anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy. We will never share your information with a third party who does not agree to maintain the confidentiality of that information using reasonable security measures. 

We use the information you provide about yourself when requesting an insurance quote only to complete that request. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your request for an insurance quote. 

In some cases, we use your personally identifiable information to provide information to you, such as to send newsletters to you that you request or to personalize the Site in accordance with your requests. 

In some situations, we share your personally identifiable information with third parties who provide services to the Site in order to enhance the functionality available to you on the Site, and to provide you with new information and services on the Site. 

Anytime you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information, for example, in chat rooms or on message boards, that information may be used by third parties. In these cases, your choice to disclose personally identifiable information is voluntary. 

We use your information on an aggregated basis to do such things as operate and enhance the Site. 

**(4) Controlling the Collection, Use and Distribution of Your Information**   
You can control the content of your personal information by following the instructions stated below in section 5. 

Please note that if you provide any information on your own or directly to parties who provide service to the Site or any other sites you encounter on the Internet (even if these sites are branded with our branding), different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. We encourage you to investigate and ask questions before disclosing information to third parties. 

**(5) Correcting and Updating Personal Information**   
You can access and update your personal information, including changing your subscriptions to our email newsletters and opting out of receiving email from us, by sending an email to Customer Assistance at [support@insuremeonline.com](mailto:support@insuremeonline.com). Even if some personal information is changed in our registration database, you acknowledge that it may still be stored on other databases (including those kept for archival purposes). 

**(6) Our Security Procedures**   
We have established and maintain reasonable security procedures to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of your personally identifiable information. These measures include firewalls, password protection, electronic monitoring and physical security of our servers. “Perfect security,” however, does not exist on the Internet. 

Although your privacy is very important to us, due to the existing legal, regulatory and security environment, we cannot fully ensure that your private communications and other personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Additionally, in the unlikely event we need to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, we can (and you authorize us to do so) disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. 

We hope this Privacy Policy clarifies our procedures regarding your personal information. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time so please re-visit this page as often as you wish. 

"When 13 carriers compete for your business, you win!" 

Get your Free quotes now!

Do you currently have car insurance?  
Yes  No
